{
    "Items": [
        {
            "question": "Which vocabulary represent to 螞蟻?",
            "chinese": "螞蟻",
			"correctAns": "Ant",
			"wrongAns": ["Aet", "Bat","Cat"]
        },
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 蝙蝠?",
			"chinese": "蝙蝠",
			"correctAns": "Bat",
			"wrongAns": ["Bird", "Bet", "Pat"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 水牛?",
			"chinese": "水牛",
			"correctAns": "Buffalo",
			"wrongAns": ["Butterfly", "Bee", "Bear"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 蝴蝶?",
			"chinese": "蝴蝶",
			"correctAns": "Butterfly",
			"wrongAns": ["Bug", "Worm", "flies" ]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 駱駝?",
			"chinese": "駱駝",
			"correctAns": "camel",
			"wrongAns": ["Cat", "Cold", "Calf", "Cub"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 恐龍?",
			"chinese": "恐龍",
			"correctAns": "dinosaur",
			"wrongAns": ["fawn", "chick", "crane", "pullet"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 麋鹿?",
			"chinese": "麋鹿",
			"correctAns": "elk",
			"wrongAns": ["eagle", "duck", "donkey", "flamingo"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 青蛙?",
			"chinese": "青蛙",
			"correctAns": "frog",
			"wrongAns": ["kit", "cub", "pup", "fingerling"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 公牛?",
			"chinese": "公牛",
			"correctAns": "ox",
			"wrongAns": ["cow", "owlet", "fledgling", "peachick"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 浣熊?",
			"chinese": "浣熊",
			"correctAns": "Raccoon",
			"wrongAns": ["bunny", "kitten", "pinkie", "rabbit"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 鯊魚?",
			"chinese": "鯊魚",
			"correctAns": "shark",
			"wrongAns": ["spiderling", "cosset", "tadpole", "poult"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Which vocabulary represent to 啄木鳥?",
			"chinese": "啄木鳥",
			"correctAns": "woodpecker",
			"wrongAns": ["joey", "calf", "pup", "hatchling"]
		}
    ]
}